# Neil Hall

Customer Retention Specialist neil4hall@gmail.com

### **Profile**

Dynamic professional with over 25 years of combined experience in full-stack programming, customer relations, inventory management, product quality control and quality assurance.

Seeking new opportunities as an entry level full-stack developer following my recent completion of the University of Toronto SCS coding boot camp.

# Skills Skill group SPA frameworks Proactive Problem solving Communication

# Experience

#### 2018 - Present

#### **Easy Home, Goeasy**

Customer Retention Specialist, North York

- Maintain communication with customers.
- Control customer's accounts.
- Process customer's payments.
- Assess and address customer complaints.
- · Conduct customer negotiations.
- Develop and implement customer retention strategies
- Actively participate in clientele building initiatives
- Provide on the job training for new staff.

#### 2016 - 2018

#### **Prodigy Parts**

Shipping Agent, Toronto

- Inspected and verified auto parts.
- Fulfilled invoices using scanners, digital ergonomics, Trello and Sequel Pro.
- Managed inventory using google sheets and Redmine applications.
- Ensured the proper storage and transportation of goods.
- Collaborated with team members, clients and management to achieve full customer satisfaction.

#### 2002 - 2016

#### **Caribbean Cement Company**

Laboratory Quality Control Coordinator, Kingston

- Setup and conducted chemical analyses.
- Conducted equipment calibrations and diagnostic checks.
- Compiled, interpreted and presented data.
- Participated in process optimization and performance improvement strategies.
- Troubleshoot and corrected software system failures.

## Contact

★ 1 Graymar road, Brampton Ontario L6S 1Z7

**1** 416-856-2537

■ neil4hall@gmail.com

2002 - 2016

**Caribbean Cement Company (continued)** 

Laboratory Quality Control Coordinator, Kingston

- Participated in management systems audits.
- Provided leadership, technical advice and training to colleagues and junior staff.

# Education

2021 - 2021

**Coding Boot camp** 

University of Toronto School of continuing st

udies, Toronto

Training included full stack programming languages and frameworks such as React,

JavaScript, Express and HTML.

1998 - 2000

Master of Science Computer Science Systems and computer Sciences

Howard University, District of Columbia Training included the design, programming, and application of computing systems.

1990 - 1995

Bachelor of Science: Chemistry and

**Biochemistry** 

University of the West indies, Kingston Training included fundamentals of chemical and biochemical processes and applications.